# Tran, Le Anh (1996)

PhD in Computer Vision

"Once the WHY is clear, the HOW goes easy"

tranleanh.github.io tranleanh.nt@gmail.com

**\( +82 10 7248 2807** 

github.com/tranleanh

Seoul, South Korea in /in/tranleanh

#### ABOUT ME -

I began my academic journey in 2014 by pursuing a degree in Automation and Control Engineering, but the appeal of AI captivated me in late 2017. Since then, I have been actively involved in various AI projects. My primary research interests that are reflected by my publications so far include image enhancement, cluster analysis, and object detection. I completed my PhD in early 2024 under the guidance of Prof. Dong-Chul Park, an expert in Artificial Neural Networks. I primarily specialize in Python programming and have experience with various frameworks such as tensorflow, pytorch, conda, etc. I am also a contributing writer for various popular Medium publications such as Towards Data Science, Level Up Coding, etc.

#### **EDUCATION** -

**PhD in Computer Vision** 3/2021 - 2/2024

Myongji University (Natural Science Campus), South Korea

3/2019 - 2/2021 **MSc in Computer Vision** 

Myongji University (Natural Science Campus), South Korea

BEng in Automation and Control Engineering (graduated with honors) 9/2014 - 8/2018

HCMC University of Technology and Education (HCMUTE), Vietnam

## **EXPERIENCE**

4/2020 - 2/2024 Research Intern

> MindinTech, Inc., Seoul, South Korea Area: Computer Vision for Intelligent Driving

3/2021 - 2/2024 **Research Assistant** 

Intelligent Computing Research Lab (ICRL), Myongji University, South Korea

Area: Image Enhancement, Cluster Analysis

**Summer Internship** 7/2019 - 9/2019

OCST Co., Ltd., Seoul, South Korea

Project: Object Detection Streaming and Data Management on Web Browser

3/2018 - 2/2019 **Al Engineer** 

FPT Software, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam Area: Computer Vision for Autonomous Driving

2/2017 - 1/2018 **Teaching Assistant** 

Faculty of Electrical and Electronics Engineering, HCMUTE, Vietnam

Subject: Electric Drivers

### **OTHERS**

# Languages

- Vietnamese (native)
- English (proficient)

# Memberships

- IEEE Member (since 2022)
- IEEE Young Professionals (since 2022)

## Work Style

- Being self-motivated and independent
- Moving from basic to complex
- Being able to learn new knowledge quickly
- Being a problem solver

| PUBLICATIONS |  |
|--------------|--|
|              | For also December 10 Martin and 10 Martin 10 M |
| 2024         | Encoder-Decoder Networks with Guided Transmission Map for Effective Image Dehazing LA Tran, DC Park The Visual Computer, Springer (SCIE)   |
| 2024         |  |
| 2024         | Cluster Analysis via Projection onto Convex Sets  LA Tran, D Kwon, HM Deberneh, DC Park  |
|              | Intelligent Data Analysis, IOS Press ( <b>SCIE</b> )   |
| 2024         | Toward Improving Robustness of Object Detectors Against Domain Shift   |
|              | LA Tran, NC Tran, DC Park, J Carrabina, D Castells-Rufas IEEE International Conference on Green Energy, Computing and Sustainable Technology (GECOST)  |
|              |  |
| 2023         | Single Image Dehazing via Regional Saturation-Value Translation  LA Tran, D Kwon, DC Park  |
|              | Procedia Computer Science  |
| 2023         | Image Compression using POCS-based Clustering Algorithm  |
|              | LA Tran, DC Park   |
|              | International Exchange and Innovation Conference on Engineering & Sciences (IEICES)  |
| 2023         | Embedding Clustering via Autoencoder and Projection onto Convex Set  LA Tran, TD Nguyen, TD Do, NC Tran, D Kwon, DC Park   |
|              | IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)  |
| 2023         | Efficient Infrared-Thermal Imaging Fusion for Human Detection in Heavy Smoke Scenarios   |
|              | NN Truong, MH Le, TD Do, LA Tran, TD Nguyen, HH Trinh  |
|              | IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)  |
| 2023         | Encoder-Decoder Network with Guided Transmission Map: Robustness and Applicability  LA Tran, DC Park   |
|              | Smart Innovation, Systems and Technologies, Vol. 333   |
| 2022         | Encoder-Decoder Network with Guided Transmission Map: Architecture   |
|              | LA Tran, DC Park International Conference on Advances in Signal Processing and Artificial Intelligence (ASDAI)   |
|              | International Conference on Advances in Signal Processing and Artificial Intelligence (ASPAI)  |
| 2022         | POCS-based Clustering Algorithm LA Tran, HM Deberneh, TD Do, TD Nguyen, MH Le, DC Park   |
|              | IEEE International Workshop on Intelligent Systems (IWIS)  |
| 2022         | Encoder-Decoder Network with Guided Transmission Map for Image Dehazing  |
|              | LA Tran, S Moon, DC Park   |
|              | Procedia Computer Science, Vol. 204  |
| 2021         | Enhancement of Robustness in Object Detection Module for ADAS  LA Tran, TD Do, DC Park, MH Le  |
|              | IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)  |
| 2020         | Object Detection Streaming and Data Management on Web Browser  |
|              | LA Tran Technical Report, OCST Co., Ltd.   |
|              |  |
| 2019         | Robust U-Net-based Road Lane Markings Detection for Autonomous Driving  LA Tran, MH Le   |
|              | IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)  |
| 2018         | A Vision-based Method for Autonomous Landing on a Target with a Quadcopter   |
|              | LA Tran, NP Le, TD Do, MH Le IEEE International Conference on Green Technology and Sustainable Development (GTSD)  |
|              |  |
| Under Review | Distilled Pooling Transformer Encoder for Efficient Image Dehazing  LA Tran, DC Park   |
| Under Review | Haze Removal via Regional Saturation-Value Translation and Soft Segmentation LA Tran, DC Park  |
| Under Review | Soft Knowledge-based Distilled Dehazing Networks LA Tran, DC Park  |
|              |  |